My name is Daniel Hershel Silber-Baker,
我叫 Daniel Hershel Silber-Baker
and I am from Oakland California.
来自加利福尼亚州奥克兰市
I grew up in Berkeley California and I currently live in Los Angeles California,
我在加州伯克利长大 现在住在洛杉矶
and this my friends is coming to you live from Mountain View studios Udacity.
这是从 Udacity 硅谷总部 加州山景城发回的报道
Really many to most of the skills that are taught in
实话实话 我在课程中教给大家的内容
the course are things that I would use every day doing web development.
都是我在日常工作中每天都要用到的
I mean, I think we're at a point now where web development
我认为异步编程
really demands a synchronicity as an option and
对 Web 开发来说是必不可少的
so the Fetch and promises this is really the meat of the new JavaScript world I think.
因此 Fetch 和 promises 是 JavaScript 世界中的关键
So I think there isn't really,
我实在想不出
it's hard for me to imagine a topic that's more relevant.
还有其他主题比它们更重要
Anytime you want to work with any web API or anything that demands a synchronicity,
只要你需要异步访问 Web API
I think Fetch and chain promises really are the solution there.
Fetch 和 promises 链就是最好的选择
After completing the course,
学完本课
students should be able to build
我希望大家具备了
their own asynchronous applications that use an external web API,
使用 Web API 独立编写异步应用的能力
and really I think that's one of the fundamental skills that
在我看来
employers are looking for now is your ability to put up
这也是雇主们特别喜欢的技能
quickly an async web app that is dynamic and can
快速构建异步 Web 应用
interact with different spaces and bring together a unique experience.
动态更新用户界面 带给用户独一无二的体验
So for me, the idea is to give you the underlying skills that would allow
我的出发点是让大家掌握基础
you to use asynchronous applications to build up whatever kind of app you're looking for.
进而有能力构建任何你想要的异步应用
Any app is going to need data coming in and out of it,
每个应用都需要请求或发送数据
and I think what we've really solidified here is that there's an elegant syntax
我们在这里学到的 Fetch API 和 promises
to the Fetch API and that promises are the best solution in this space.
不失为一种优雅的解决方案
So putting together this course,
总结一下
my hope is that by the end of it,
我希望大家学完后
you'll have at least one portfolio project,
至少可以为自己的项目集里
an app that you'll be able to put into your portfolio,
增加一个异步 Web 应用项目
and I think another important thing is to match
我认为还有一件事也很重要
your code with any app that you put up in a portfolio.
你需要把代码和项目集关联起来
So this would be a good chance if you haven't already to start a GitHub.
如果你还没有使用 GitHub 那么不妨一试
One thing I've found is that GitHub repos are
我发现应聘时经常要求提供
commonly asked for in job applications situations.
GitHub 的地址
So this would give you an instance where you have a project you can put
这样既可以把项目加入你的项目集
up on your portfolio and a code repo that you can
也可以把代码托管在
create in GitHub so that people can see you know how to work
GitHub 人们观察你的 GitHub 记录
back and forth from different branches and make things happen.
就能知道你是怎么把项目做出来的
So this nano degree program should really put you
学完前端开发纳米学位
on the course to be able to apply it to some real-world jobs.
你就可以尝试将学到的知识用于日常工作
I think some ones you might be well-suited to look into really anything on the front end,
你们当中的优秀者或许可以尝试申请和前端相关的职位
front end engineer, something having to do with UX or UI or a common web developer.
前端开发工程师 或者和 UX UI 相关的网页开发者
Once you have these skills to make asynchronous applications that include data,
当你掌握了开发异步应用的技能
you're really well equipped to do
你就可以从事
web development and eventually to do front end and engineering.
Web 开发相关的职位 并且最终成为一名前端工程师
In my experience, hiring managers are really
根据我的经验 招聘经理最喜欢
looking for people who understand the logic of what they're doing.
清楚事物内在逻辑的工程师
It's one of the reasons that throughout the course,
这就是为什么贯穿整个课程
we really try to make sure you understand each step and why you're doing it.
我不断帮助大家理解每一步为什么要那样做的原因
I think usually people want someone who can come up with creative solutions,
通常人们希望找到可以拿出创造性方案的工程师
and to do creative solutions,
要做到这样
you really need to have a repertoire of what the tools are at your disposal.
你必须知道你的工具箱里有些什么
My hope is that through this process,
我希望通过这一过程
you'll build your tool sets so that in any situation,
你为自己的工具箱添加了趁手的工具
you could show your different skills as you
在面对任何问题时
navigate the particulars of any issue that you're facing,
你都能找出合适的技术解决
the process of making this course.
在制作这个课程的过程中
I really feel like I've got to watch it come alive.
我真是一步步看着它变成这个样子
At the beginning, I'm just typing on a computer or trying to
刚开始的时候 我在电脑前不停工作
figure out a different arrangement for Google Docs and Google sheets
使用 Google Docs 和 Google sheets 尝试了各种组合
and then really when it comes alive is when I get to
最终我将它带到了各位面前
give it to the world when I present the possibility to other people.
等待大家的评判
So our first step has been done here this week as we all get together as a team and
教与学是一体的 我们已经在这一周内
make sure that we have everything set to offer you the best programming that we can.
将最好的编程实践带给了大家 走完了第一步
But the real excitement comes now that it's to you,
现在轮到你了
we want to see what you'll do with this.
看看你能用这些技术做点什么